HAEMIN RYU

[he min ryoo]



Seoul, South Korea

(GPA: 3.56/4.0)

My vision is to enrich and diversify the interaction between users and computers by creating novel experiences with emerging technology to make products accessible to people, regardless of disability and age.

My interests rest at the intersection of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI), Universal Design, VR, and Accessibility.

EDUCATION

Purdue University B. S. in Computer Science

Jan. 2018-Dec. 2019

Fort Wayne, IN, USA (GPA: 3.71/4.0)

Seoul Women's University B. S. in Computer Science

Mar. 2014-Feb. 2020

Honors: Merit-based Scholar, Dual Degree Program Scholar

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Honors: Top 50, Dual Degree Program Scholar

Software Developer Cirrus ABS Corporation (MarketSnare)

Jan. 2020-Present

- Delivered a local marketing web platform 'MarketSnare' that meets multi-location business needs with centralized management, localization, and customization for various regions.
- Developed web solutions with the MarketSnare software platforms using the Microsoft ASP.NET framework, C#, XML, XSLT, JSON, HTML/CSS/JS, API integrations, Database management, and Web Server Technologies.
- Highlighted projects: A&L Great Lakes Laboratories, Anthem Retail Program, ADT localized sites, Service Experts, IWDC

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

[2] Menu interfaces to Avoid Disembodiment Situations in Virtual Reality

Advisor: Dr. Beomjin Kim 2022-Present

- Analyzed different menu styles environment to investigate the way to help improve menu interface design in Virtual Reality focused on the disembodiment issue.
- Tested menu interfaces in a Virtual Reality environment with a young age group and compared the result with the expectation of menu efficiency.

[1] Improvement to Pix2Code using Fast.ai: Automatic Generation of GUI with a Model Classification

Jan. 2020-Apr. 2020

Advisor: Dr. Venkata Inukollu - Proved that automated deep learning model classification using Fast.ai can improve the accuracy and speed of the Pix2Code GUI Generation.

SELECTED PROJECTS

[2] PLUR: Online Platform for Physical Education Community for Individuals with Disabilities

#Accessibility #Crowdsourcing #Sports #Community

Oct. 2021

- Created a web app that uses local resources and crowdsourcing to make sports programs and facilities more accessible to individuals with disabilities.
- Developed scenarios for connecting differently abled children and young adults with verified local coaches, trainers, sports associations, and clubs to begin their journey in sports.

[1] Indoor Navigation: Improved Accessibility for People with Disabilities

FUNDED BY * PARKVIEW

#Accessibility #DataVisualization #Navigation #Hospital

Aug. 2019-Apr. 2020

- Leveraged hospital navigation data from beacon technology focused on the patient experience to provide a more accessible hospital visit experience for patients with disabilities.
- Designed a data analytics web application to discover heavy/light usage facilities and routes at the hospital and improved mobile application navigation to assist patients.
- Built a web interface that visualizes interactive data analytics and displays employee administration management systems using Angular 7, TypeScript, and HTML/CSS/JS.

AWARDS AND HONORS

Academic Conferences

Oct. 2022	ACM UIST Travel Award	ACM UIST 2022, USD 1,338
Jul. 2020	IEEE/ACM ICSE 2020 Student Mentoring Workshop	IEEE/ACM ASE 2019, USD 500
Oct. 2019	Student Travel Fund Grant for IEEE/ACM ASE 2019	Purdue Global, USD 1,164.83

Scholastic Achievements

Apr. 2020	Student Research and Creative Endeavor Symposium - Poster	Purdue FW Research & Innovation
Apr. 2019	Purdue Fort Wayne Top 50 Award	Purdue FW Top 50 Committee
2018, 2019	Dean's List & Semester Honors List	Purdue FW College of ETCS
2018, 2019	Dual Degree Program Scholarship, 2-year Full Tuition	SWU Division of International Affairs
2014. 2015	Seoul Women's University Merit-based Scholarship, 2-semester Full Tuition	SWU College of Informatics & Media

Collaborative Project Achievements

Oct. 2021	Hack for Humanity - Top 7 Finalist	Arizona State University & StateFarm
Feb. 2021	Flipping Finance Challenge - 1 st & 2 nd Places	Indiana Bond Bank, USD 270
May. 2019	Senior Capstone Design Project Excellence Award - 2 nd Place	Purdue FW Dept. of Computer Science
Nov. 2015	Creative Idea Competition Award - 1st Place	SWU Creative Center, USD 279
Jul. 2015	LIKELION Ideathon - Top 10 Out of 110 projects & 500 college students	LIKELION

INVITED TALKS AND PANELS

Nov. 2na, 2022 Apr. 8th, 2022	Lightning Talks UX Design for Web Developers	University of Illinois Web Conference
Panels		
Apr. 15th, 2022	Q & A with Engineering, Technology & Computer Science Alumni	Purdue FW College of ETCS

Apr. 10th, 2022	& & A With Engineering, reclinology & Computer Science Admini	r drade i vv College of E1C5
Apr. 12th, 2021	Engineering, Technology & Computer Science Internship Panel	Purdue FW College of ETCS
Nov. 20th, 2019	"A Day in their Shoes" Simulation with Panel Discussion	Purdue FW International Week

Guest Lecture

Oct. 2021 Journey on Conference on Automated Software Engineering Purdue FW Software Engineering class

VOLUNTEER AND TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Academic Service

Speaker

Oct. 2022, 2021, 2020	ACM UIST 2022, 2021, 2020 Student Volunteer
May. 2021	ACM CHI 2021 Student Volunteer
Jul. 2020	IEEE/ACM ICSE 2020 Student Volunteer

UX/UI Designer

Aug. 2021–Mar. 2022	United Nations SDSN Global Youth Seed Fund Initiative
Aug 2021_Oct 2021	College di Lond Like a Cirl Challenge Drainet for Volum Women Lo

Aug. 2021–Oct. 2021 Go Laadli Lead Like a Girl Challenge Project for Young Women Leaders

Leadership

Feb. 2020 ACM Global Game Jam Fort Wayne Site Organizer

Jul. 2017–Aug. 2017 Dongan Intellectual and Developmental Disabilities Retreat Volunteer

Teaching Assistant

Fall 2018–Fall 2019	[CS 36000] Software Engineering with Professor. Venkata Inukollu
Summer 2019	[CS 16000] Intro to Computer Science I (Java) with Professor. David Liu

Tutoring

Fall 2018–Spring 2019 Core Academic Skills Assessment (CASA) - Mathematics

Mar. 2016–Nov. 2016 NAVER Connect Fdn. Play with Software - Programming education for elementary school students